<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>FSMNLP 2023 in Stellenbosch - Paper Submission, CFP</title><link href="https://fsmnlp2023.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://fsmnlp2023.github.io/feeds/paper-submission-cfp.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://fsmnlp2023.github.io/</id><updated>2022-10-18T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Call for Papers</title><link href="https://fsmnlp2023.github.io/call-for-papers.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-10-18T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-10-18T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>FSMNLP 2023 organizing team</name></author><id>tag:fsmnlp2023.github.io,2022-10-18:/call-for-papers.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The conference invites papers related to themes including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NLP applications and linguistic aspects of finite-state methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finite-state models of language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practices for building and evaluating morphological models for the world’s languages using finite-state technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machine learning of finite-state models of natural language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finite-state manipulation software …&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The conference invites papers related to themes including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NLP applications and linguistic aspects of finite-state methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finite-state models of language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practices for building and evaluating morphological models for the world’s languages using finite-state technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machine learning of finite-state models of natural language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finite-state manipulation software and tools with relevance to NLP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Important dates&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;deadline of submission: tbd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;notification: tbd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;camera-ready version: tbd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Submissions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Papers must present original, unpublished research and implementation results. Simultaneous submissions to FSMNLP and to another conference or workshop are not allowed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FSMNLP accepts two kinds of submissions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;long papers (8 pages excluding references and appendices) reporting completed, significant research,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;short papers (4 pages excluding references and appendices) reporting ongoing work and partial results, implementations, grammars, practical tools, interactive software demos, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Short papers are expected to be presented as system demos, posters and/or short presentations, while long papers are presented in full talks. Accepted long papers can be extended by one page in order to deal with the criticism in the reviews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All submissions are electronic and only in PDF format via EasyChair. Authors have to prepare their papers in LaTeX using the ACL 2019 style files to produce the PDF document. The zip archive of the style files can be downloaded here: &lt;a href="https://www.orchid.inf.tu-dresden.de/fsmnlp2019/assets/pdf/340-acl2019-latex.zip"&gt;ACL 2019 style&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the submission and reviewing is double blind, information about the author(s) and other identifying information such as obvious self-references (e.g., “We showed in [12] …”) and financial or personal acknowledgements should be omitted in the submitted papers whenever feasible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A paper may contain a clearly marked appendix and data files to support its claims. This material will not be published. While reviewers are urged to consult this extra material for better comprehension, it is at their discretion whether they do so. Such extra material should also be anonymized to the extent feasible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Papers must be submitted electronically in PDF format via &lt;a href="https://easychair.org/"&gt;easychair&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It is excepted that&lt;/em&gt; all accepted papers will be published and archived in the FSMNLP 2023 proceedings in the ACL Anthology. For this the authors should grant the appropriate copyright.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Computational Challenge&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Potentially we borrow some hardware/software from WARA M&amp;amp;L to do something of a challenge with hidden data sets.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Paper Submission, CFP"></category></entry></feed>