<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>FSMNLP 2023 in Stellenbosch - Paper Submission, CFP</title><link href="https://fsmnlp2023.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://fsmnlp2023.github.io/feeds/paper-submission-cfp.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://fsmnlp2023.github.io/</id><updated>2022-08-27T00:00:00+02:00</updated><subtitle>28-30th of August 2023</subtitle><entry><title>Call for Papers</title><link href="https://fsmnlp2023.github.io/call-for-papers.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-08-27T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-08-27T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>FSMNLP 2023 organizing team</name></author><id>tag:fsmnlp2023.github.io,2022-08-27:/call-for-papers.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Submissions on &lt;a href="https://www.easychair.org/conferences/?conf=fsmnlp2023"&gt;easychair&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submissions are made in two stages, a submission of a preliminary abstract
later followed by a submission of the paper itself. Papers must present
original, unpublished research and implementation results. Simultaneous
submissions to FSMNLP and to another conference or workshop are allowed.
According to the &lt;a href="https://www.aclweb.org/archive/policies/current/double-submission-policy.html"&gt;ACL double …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Submissions on &lt;a href="https://www.easychair.org/conferences/?conf=fsmnlp2023"&gt;easychair&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submissions are made in two stages, a submission of a preliminary abstract
later followed by a submission of the paper itself. Papers must present
original, unpublished research and implementation results. Simultaneous
submissions to FSMNLP and to another conference or workshop are allowed.
According to the &lt;a href="https://www.aclweb.org/archive/policies/current/double-submission-policy.html"&gt;ACL double submission policy&lt;/a&gt;,
doubly-submitted papers should indicate this fact on the title page. If
accepted at both FSMNLP and the other meeting, such a paper must be withdrawn
from one of them. Withdrawal from FSMNLP shall be as soon as possible but no
later than one week after the notification of acceptance at FSMNLP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FSMNLP accepts two kinds of submissions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;long papers (8 pages excluding references) reporting completed, significant
research,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;short papers (4 pages excluding references) reporting ongoing work
and partial results, implementations, grammars, practical tools,
interactive software demos, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Short papers are expected to be presented as system demos, posters and/or
short presentations, while long papers are presented in full talks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All submissions are electronic and in PDF format via a web-based submission
server. Authors are strongly encouraged to preparte their papers in LaTeX
using the ACL 2021-12 style files to produce the PDF document. The zip archive
of the style files can be downloaded &lt;a href="https://github.com/acl-org/acl-style-files/releases/tag/2021-12"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information about the author(s) and other identifying information such as
obvious self-references (e.g., “We showed in [12] …”) and financial or
personal acknowledgements should be omitted in the submitted papers whenever
feasible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Papers must be submitted electronically in PDF on &lt;a href="https://www.easychair.org/conferences/?conf=fsmnlp2023"&gt;easychair&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A paper may contain a clearly marked appendix and data files to support its
claims. This material will not be published. While reviewers are urged to
consult this extra material for better comprehension, it is at their
discretion whether they do so. Such extra material should also be anonymized
to the extent feasible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Paper Submission, CFP"></category></entry></feed>